Jai Hind Welcome to the new informative video
friends, today in this video we will
talk about ICC Bank's
policy for its customers, Health 360, some
things have been revised in it, so this is a video for your health,
so you must watch this video till the
end because today if there is
health then there is wealth and this product which
ICC Bank has taken in collaboration with Lombard
for its customers, this policy
is such that it is not just a health policy
but it has a lot of features, many many,
so friends let's start the video,
first if you talk about it, if I give you a
small introduction for it, then the most important thing is
that it is very extensive
and competitive, it is convenient and in this,
along with health, focus has also been given on your wellness, that is, along with the
health policy,
this policy has been made keeping your health in mind as well, in which
you will get points, if your
health is good throughout the year then
you will get points, you will be able to redeem those points, so if
you must have seen such a health policy, then
this is ICC Bank,
you can term it for 1 kg.  Let me tell you, this is only
for the customers of ICC Bank. If you do
not have an account, then you can open an account
and take a policy. So let's move ahead in the video. After that, if you see, what was there in the traditional policy in India earlier, that is, you take normal health insurance. When you have insurance, you go to the hospital and you will get the bill cashless,
you will redeem it. This was the only
help policy or part,
but today ICC Bank has
modified this entire help policy through wellness program, in which
your activity, try, health coach,
diet plan, health checkup, that is,
nothing has been included in it, so on your entire
wealth and on your health, that is, the bank has to take
care of your money and also take
care of your health. So,
overall, it has
brought a very good policy for its customers. So,
let's move ahead in the policy. The
features that you will get in it,
you can take a health policy of Rs. 10 lakh to Rs. 50 lakh in it.  The
hospital expense of Rs 1 lakh to 50 lakhs includes
day care and
treatment as well. After that, there is
also post-mortem benefit. You can avail the benefit of 60 days before 19 days.
After this,
you can also avail the treatment through AYUSH fertilization. There is
unlimited reset benefit in this,
meaning if someone gets it for one disease, then
you can get the sum assured for any other disease except you.
Additional sum injured is increased by 10%.
If your claim is
free, then the sum assured will increase up to a
maximum of 100%. There is home
health care benefit, there is claim
protector, there is health checkup and tax, which means
that by taking this policy, you will not have any problem of health tax.
Apart from this, what is there in it, you have
sum assured protector, there is
360 program through which we had talked about sum assured
and user can manage their
life style.
With this policy you can prepare for any disease and the ambulance tax
is extended, the patient is
covered after 30 days, the
disease protector is after 30 days,
if you take a new policy and after 30 days the tax
of the entire policy gets waived in it,
because many new policies have a
calling period of 3 months, 6 months also,
but there is no such period in this,
after 30 days you have to pay some tax, now let us talk about
its features,
what are the features of this policy, if we
go into its features, then this policy is so well
modified, it is between 10 lakhs to 50 lakhs, the
biggest thing in this policy, if we look at it, then let me tell you that the
patient treatment in this is
your treatment, the post license which is the
hospital is for 60 days and post authorization 90,
whose match is done after clearing 60 and 19, that means
if you have any problem, then first
you should consult an OPD or a normal doctor.  If you are
seen in the Mohalla,
after that if you are tested and it is found in the test
that brother has this disease, then first you are
admitted to Banda, then
after that there is treatment for it.
When the doctor discharges him, he has to
tell you about the time for 90 days, whether you have to
take medicine or have a checkup, so sir, that
means whatever expenses you have for 60 days before and 90 days of discharge,
you can take it within this, there is care benefit, after
waiting for 30 days, you can
declare the initial waiting period and
accept it, there is
data experience, in this there is unlimited
reset benefit, in this there is design and
ambulance,
air at 10% and up to 100% is also there, domestic
road ambulance, in this there is home health
care, health checkup, daily consultant,
you can take second option A option, there is health
assistant, wellness program, claim
protector, sub protector, C
protector, this means that such
result of ICC Bank is given by  Lombard, the
group company, has brought it. Now if
you see the premium, it
is very cheap compared to other companies. If you
talk about premiums, then it is of 10 lakh, 15 lakh,
20 lakh, 25 lakh and 50 lakh. If you
look carefully at your PM, which
is the first bucket, then 21 to 25 means one who
is between 21 to 25 years and
is an individual adult, if the individual has a policy
relief, then he needs to pay ₹465,
that too with GST.
What happens after this, if there is one adult and one
child, then 5236 needs to be paid. If there are
one adult and two children, then 6252 needs to be paid. If there are
two adults, then it is 5965. If there are two adults
and one child, then it is
7943. Two adults get
30095. Now if we look at 10 lakh, the maximum is
50 lakh. Now
in any health policy, if you go for a policy of 50 lakh, then the
premium is very high.  It
happens that you can check other companies by Googling
or
you can download the browser by talking to the customer care of the company.
I have downloaded this browser
and have brought it
for you. If we look at 50 lakhs and now if
we look at the average further, then if in the age group of 31 to 35
years, you can get a
policy of ₹50000 for ₹7000,
50 lakhs is a huge amount in which a person
can live tension free and if ever
something needs to happen for his health, then a
help policy is a must for
everyone. What is there after that, if you
are married, an adult, have children with you, then if there are
two adults and one child, then it is ₹120194. If there are two adults and
two children, you have ₹1625, which is a
very cheap policy for 25 lakhs. If you
look at the next bucket, if you are between 31 to 35 and have
two children, then it is ₹
13796. If you are in the next bucket between 36 to 40, then  It
is 14421, so even if you go for 10 lakhs, if
you see 60,
you can take the policy even for 5260 beyond 60 and the premium is
49500.
After this, let me tell you that this
product is the entire product of ICC Bank, which is
made keeping in mind its customers, so if we see the
health checkup benefits in it, there are
some in it, in it there are those from 10 lakhs to 20 lakhs
and 25 lakhs to 50 lakhs, both have been kept
in separate bowls, so there are some in it,
checkups etc. are also given free of
cost in it and
how much you will get in a year, I will tell you in the video
later, see the cap
points in it, let me tell you in the term conditions,
we were talking about these cap conditions,
what is this term condition, which is the eligibility
criteria, so exclusive offering, you are an
ICC Bank customer or inside member,
means ICC Bank wants to insure its customers that
Bhaiya, in which
its customers
who have a health policy can take it, in
which adults from 21 years to 60 years can
take it and children from 91 days to
people up to 20 years can take it and the
charges that you should keep in mind, if you have children then only
children up to 20 years can take it,
after 21 years they will be reduced to adult,
child bill is in the tax, D floater
plan only and if there is ten then it is for one year, so it is
not a big deal, every policy is
for one year, so after one year
you will get renewed, in this you
can take whose policy, in the family you
can take your own, you can take
dependent parents, you
can take defending Shivling
and you can take 20 years, that means you can take two children
and the maximum age of the child should be
20 years,
see in this, the policy which is medical,
you must have seen in many help policies that
as you take a policy, then a doctor becomes available for medical check.  They
come, they check and
go but what is there in this, there is daily
unwaiting, that too for people above 55 years of age,
if people above 55 years of age avail the policy, then
they will get a call on the phone
and they will be asked for complete details
whether they have any disease or not and the normal
query of a doctor and a patient,
they will make their query and then submit the report
or else your policy will be issued
that there is no concern in it, the
waiting period, I
discussed with you about the waiting period, it is a waiting period of 30 days,
after that you
can take some claim, that means you see
what is the calling period, there is a calling period of 30 days,
but within this also,
except for an accident, if you have a policy due to any reason, then that will be covered,
what happens after that, there are
many specific diseases and the
disease is covered only after 30 days,
if you see the list of these diseases, then there is a list of diseases
also, if you want you can go to Lombard's
website and  You
can download and see the inclusions in it
which are not taxed, such as contractures,
cataracts, apart from this, there are many such
gastric diseases, many
stone-related diseases, which are diseases and
types of arrhythmias, hydrocele, meaning
all these diseases, you do
not have to pay tax for 30 days, after 30 days you will have to pay tax on them as well. The
list of non-travel items in it has many
hospital
benefits, the final bill you get contains
many things which are taxed,
you have to pay for them, so normally it is
baby food, baby charges, beauty
service, belt press, bath, that is, these
normal things which you are getting, like
masks, then you have to pay for all these,
it has to be done in the policy everywhere.
Apart from this, if you look at the
major benefit which
ICC Bank has in digital, it is very ahead in digital,
so they have also created an app,
if you take a policy, you
can track the tax inside the app and it is a digital policy.
You will also get an A card inside it.
You can discuss it in the tally center limit
and nearby.
You can upload all the documents on this application and
upload them within 24 hours and you will get a response and you can
send it and get your claim money. Whatever
process has been done, start the claim by
filing the form, file the form, point
documents, upload as many discharge summaries
and you can track your
claim, where your video claim has
reached and the claim process is also very
easy. If you see in it,
after trying it, you
can check the iCare application or you can call the toll free number
18002 for support
or if you have any concern regarding the recording of this policy, then
you can find out by calling customer care. So
friends, I hope
that the video is very
informative, so you
must refer it to your friends and family and if you want to take this help policy,
in today's date there are two things, health
policy and Trump Plan, a
person must have something, this  There should be two policies, so let's
end the video with this, thank you.